不
No!
快看
Look! Look!
对不起  我只是  不
Sorry. Sorry. I'm just -- No.
不  那边可能有房子
No. It might be a house.
我们可以躲在里面
We could hide.
我们得继续跑
快跑
Go.
行尸走肉
第十一季  第六集
我一个人骑马耗时更短
We'll make better time if I ride out on my own.
更多人去的话
It's less risky,
风险更小  还能搜索更多地方
and we're gonna cover more ground with a larger group.
委员会正在制定计划
The Council's working on a plan right now.
康妮可没时间等委员会了
Connie doesn't have time to wait on a committee.
我们何不兼顾快速和安全呢
Well, why don't we split the difference between fast and safe?
两人一组  我们可以将地图划分为更小的格子
Teams of two. We could divide the map up into smaller grids.
这样能减少风险
It could reduce the risk.
有人看见凯利了吗
Hey. Any of you seen Kelly?
北边
走哪条路
在塔楼转弯吗  不确定
好
Okay.
我搜了整栋房子
I checked the whole house.
我们很安全  这里没人
We're okay. Nobody's here.
你需要...
You need --
"You need...
休息一下
some rest."
你好几天没睡了
You haven't slept in days.
我来放哨
"I can keep watch."
我们会找到
"We will find...
你的家
your home."
你睡吧
You...sleep.
不安全
听着
Listen.
休息吧
Rest.
好
Okay.
我再去搜一遍房子
说出他们在哪里
Tell us where they are!
反正我也没事干
My dance card's wide open, man.
我们有一整天时间
We got all day.
看不惯吗
This bother you?
我做过更糟的事
I've done worse.
那你去试试吧
Why don't you take a turn, then?
让他快点开口
Speed things up for me.
好  我来
All right. I'm up.
想得美
Like hell you are!
我们是打算僵在这里  含情脉脉地盯着彼此
Well, are we just gonna stand here staring at each other dreamily
还是直入主题
or are we gonna get to it?
你要是杀了他
Hey, you kill him,
咱俩就没完了
the two of us are gonna have a problem!
我不需要保姆
Don't need a babysitter.
我知道自己在干什么
I know what I'm doing.
告诉他们你朋友们的藏身处
Just give 'em a location, where your friends are hiding.
说了就不用受苦了
You do that, this all goes away.
这
That's, uh...
这真是个好提议
That's a good offer.
或者  听我说
Or -- and hear me out...
你们都去吃屎吧
you all could go eat shit instead.
只是个建议
Just a thought.
这些我都已经做过了
Already gone through these steps.
也许我们可以开始割点肉了
Maybe we start taking pieces.
该做什么你就做吧
You do what you gotta do.
给他一把刀
Give him a knife.
我觉得你还不明白
I don't think you understand.
我是你最好的机会
I'm the best shot you got.
为什么  我们现在是"朋友"了吗
Why? We "Friends" now?
不  不是因为我们是朋友
No. Not 'cause we're friends.
而是因为我拿着刀
'Cause I'm the one holding the knife.
嗯
Yeah.
你的哥们还拿着枪呢
And your buddy's the one holding the gun.
闭嘴
Shut up!
闭嘴  听我说
Shut up and listen to me.
我知道你跟她很亲近
I know you're close to her.
那个首领
The leader.
亲近到知道他们藏在哪里
Close enough to know where they're hidin'.
不必有人死在这里
No one needs to die in here.
所以快说出地点  这样就皆大欢喜了
So just say a location so we can all walk away happy.
去死吧  混...
Go to hell, assho--
地点
Location!
否则我再切一根
Or I take another!
我不能说
I can't!
地点
Location!
-不  求你停下来  -地点
- No! No! Please stop! - Location!
黄房子
Yellow house.
283号公路附近的小镇
Town off the 283.
有天线  有天线  有天线
Antenna. Antenna. Antenna. Antenna.
行了吗
Is that good enough?
我可以去侦察
I can scout it out.
带上一支小队  你们三个都去
Take a squad. Three of you.
看看我们的朋友是不是说了真话
See if our friend speaks truth.
你要我们带他一起去吗
You want us to take him?
你看起来"好极了"
老剃刀
这里还有人
等等  发生了什么
Wait. What happened?
房子里还有人
慢点  我不懂
S-Slow down. I don't understand.
它在墙后面  盯着我
什么
What --
还有人
看着没动静
Looks quiet. No movement.
有两个入口  我们同时进入吗
Two entrances. Breach both?
两人一组  你带上鲍威尔
By twos. You take Powell.
华盛顿  菲施  绕到黄房子后面去
Washington, Fish, go around the back of the yellow house.
那个白痴呢
What about dickhead?
我难道要相信他会保护我吗
Am I supposed to believe he's got my back?
不  那是我的职责
No, that's my job.
永远如此
Always.
没人
Clear!
都没人  卡弗
It's all clear, Carve.
那混蛋耍了我们
That son of a bitch jerked us around.
我们应该留在屋子里  到处看看
We should stay, look around for a bit,
以防有遗漏
so we don't miss nothing.
不  我们先搜查整个小镇
No, we'll search the rest of the town first.
动作要快  动静要小  他们说不定还在附近
Quick and quiet, in case they're still nearby.
你们三个  从北边往里搜
You three, take the north end and work back.
-我们在中间碰头  -明白
- We'll meet you in the middle. - Copy.
A:被困在行尸之中
与它们同行了很多天
没有灯  没有食物  水很少
B:米琼恩告诉我的
A:她在哪里
B:不知道  她出去找人了
我本希望能见到她
A:我们似乎被监视了
B:天色已晚
我们天一亮
就收拾东西出发
你在哪
Where are you?
我爷爷的房子墙里也有这种隔层
My grandfather's house used to have one of these.
我会偷偷往里面塞东西
I'd secretly shove stuff in there.
不好意思  我什么都没看见
I-I'm sorry. I don't see anything.
里面有东西
我相信你看到了某些东西
I'm sure you saw something...
不过
but...
不过你一直没睡
But you haven't slept.
所以也许是
So maybe it's...
嗯  因为
Y-Yeah. 'Cause...
好吧  对不起
Okay, okay. Okay. I'm sorry.
我们再搜一次房子  好吗
You and me, let's give the house another sweep, okay?
我不要待在这里
康妮
Connie!
没人
Clear!
这边
Over here!
还是湿的
They're still wet.
看来他说的是真话
Guess he was telling the truth, then.
我们该搜搜其它房间
We should clear the other rooms.
-没人  -没人
- Clear! - Clear!
没人
Clear!
没发现
Nothing.
也许他们从后门走了  我能追踪他们
Maybe they went out the back. I can track them.
你急着走吗
Are you in a hurry to leave?
什么
What?
在刚才的房子里  你希望我们留下
Other building, you wanted to stick around
确保没有遗漏
and make sure we didn't miss anything.
现在你又想走了  你到底想怎样
Now you wanna run right off. Which is it?
听着  我只是想帮忙
Look, man, I'm just trying to help.
但你一直在哔哔
Yet you keep chirpin'.
好吧  要是跟丢了就怪你  可不怪我
Fine. You lose 'em, it's on you. It ain't on me.
别说了
Stop.
华盛顿  查一下周围
Wash, we need a perimeter check.
可能有人跑了  半公里范围
Possible runners. Half a klick.
收到  肖
Copy that, Shaw.
听着  我没时间听你们斗嘴
Look. I don't have time for this toddler bullshit.
-听着  -我知道
- Listen -- - I know.
我明白  但我不需要
I understand, but I don't need it.
去搜楼上  确保没有遗漏
Go sift upstairs, make sure we didn't miss anything.
别
Don't.
别做什么
Don't what?
你要么跟我们一边  要么不是
You're either with us or you're not.
你希望我做什么
What do you want me to do?
首先  别惹怒卡弗
For one thing... stop pissing off Carver.
一般都没好下场
Usually don't end well.
快走
Come on.
拜托
Please.
拜托  再
Please. Just a --
再走几步
Just a little bit... more!
凯利
Kelly?
太棒了
Awesome.
需要帮助吗
You need help?
你在想什么呢
What the hell were you thinking?
你该告诉我们你要出来
You should have told us that you were heading out.
过来
Come here.
我没事
I'm fine.
但康妮有事
But Connie's not.
我找到了她的营地
I found her camp.
她跟一个认识米琼恩的人在一起
She's with some guy who knew Michonne.
他们匆忙离开  情况不对劲
They left in a hurry. Something's not right.
她觉得他们被跟踪了
She thought they were being followed.
她在外面
She's out there.
她很害怕
She's scared.
她需要我
She needs me.
如果
And if...
如果她出了事
if something happened to her...
不会的  我们会先找到她
No. We're gonna find her first.
对
Yeah.
来  我们走吧
Come on. Let's get movin'.
饿
Hungry!
天啊  康妮
Oh, God. Connie.
来吧  我帮你  来吧
Come on. I got you. Come on.
天啊
Oh, God.
他们跑掉了  不会回来了
They ran. They ain't comin' back here.
什么
What?
仔细想想  你们重创了他们
I mean, think about it. You hit 'em hard.
就算他们人更多  也不会回来了
Even if they get more people, they won't come back here.
这不明智
It's a bad move.
你们在镇上有二十人
You got what? 20 people in your town.
你们有武器  围墙
You got weapons. You got walls.
远远就能看见他们接近
You'd see them coming from a mile away.
相信我  他们跑了
Trust me. They ran.
你这么做是有什么目的吗
Is there a point to any of this?
走吧
Let's go.
这里没人  该走了
There's nothing here. It's time we move on.
不  我们错过了什么
No. We're missing something.
-行  再浪费一个小时  真聪明  -达里尔
- Fine. Let's waste another hour. That's smart. - Daryl --
他蠢到稀里糊涂不是我的错
It's not my fault he's too stupid to pay attention!
哔哔哔
Yeah. Chirp, chirp, chirp.
-够了  -拉倒
- Enough. - Ah, screw that.
这浑球想玩  我就教教他规矩
This dirtbag wants to play, I'll teach him the rules.
我就在这里  动手啊
I'm right here, man. Make a move.
现在不是时候  你也无权下令
This is not the time, and it's not your call to make.
老天啊  肖
Jesus, Shaw.
我们都知道他的真实面目
We both know who he really is deep down.
什么
What?
我当时在场  记得吗
I was there. Remember?
之后
After.
你以为这次会有不同的结果吗
What, you think this is gonna end any different?
所以你是在做什么  守护我吗
So this is what? You looking out for me?
永远如此
Always.
我懂了
Gotcha.
那大火那次呢
And what about the fire?
教皇把我锁在木屋里  放火烧我
When Pope locked me in the cabin and lit it up.
你一定事先知道的
You must have known.
那也是你在守护我吗
Was that you looking out for me, too?
肖  醒醒吧
Shaw. Wake up.
现在的一切都是考验
Everything's a test now.
如果你以为这家伙在乎我们
If you think this guy is ever gonna give a shit about any of us,
你会失败的
you're gonna fail.
他说得对
No, he's right.
我根本不在乎你们
I don't give a shit about any of you.
除了你
Except you.
我为你而来
I'm here for you.
我犯过错  这不是秘密
It's no secret. I made mistakes.
但我现在来了
But I'm here right now.
也许这次我能做得更好  如果你允许的话
Maybe I'd be better at it this time, if you'd let me.
而且教皇令我很害怕
And Pope scares the shit outta me.
我可不想被他用脚踩进火堆里
I don't wanna be face-first in the fire under his boot.
但如果你要我信任他们  我会照做
But if you say trust 'em, I'll trust 'em.
我们在这里浪费足够多时间了
We've wasted enough time here already.
你不是真的要...
Oh, you're not seriously gonna --
该走了
It's time to move on.
好吧  听你的
Sure. Your call.
等等
Hold on.
早说没人了
Told ya.
走哪边
Which way?
我们可以分开  搜索两条路  然后回来
We could split up, check both trails, double back.
暴雨快来了  我们应该聚在一起
Storm's coming. We should stick together.
你来定  你觉得她走了哪边
It's up to you. Which way do you think she went?
那边
That way.
他们把我们引到了这里
They led us here.
我从没见过这么丧失人性的人
I've never seen people this far gone.
把我们像猎物一样驱赶
To herd us, like prey.
但我们不是猎物
But we're not.
我会救你出去
I'm getting you out.
我们会尽力一搏
We'll make a run for it.
拿着
Take this.
不管发生什么
No matter what happens...
你都得一直跑
you have to keep going.
无论有没有我  都别停下
With or without me. Don't stop.
不能回头...
Just keep...
不
不不不  拜托了
No. No, no, no, no, no. Please.
拿着吧
Just take it.
要出去就一起出去
我不会让你放弃
我不知道该怎么解释
I don't know how to explain.
但我没有选择
But I don't have a choice.
我迷失过...很长一段时间
I lost myself... for a long time.
完全迷失了
Off the map.
我
And I, um...
做过一些无法挽回的选择
I made choices that I can't un-choose.
但她给了我第二次机会
But she gave me another chance.
米琼恩
Michonne.
她为我指明了道路
She pointed me back to the road,
而这条路让我找到了你
and somehow that road led right to you.
所以我必须放弃这个机会
So I have to pass on that chance,
不然一切就没意义了
or it all means nothing.
如果你能
And if you can...
If you...
找到你的家人
can find your family...
我们一起走
不
No, no. No.
听着
Listen, listen, listen.
我需要你向我保证
I need you to promise me
你不会回头  不管发生什么
that you will keep going, no matter what happens.
一起
Together?
Together.
时候到了
Time's up.
快走
Go. Go. Go, go. Go, go!
Go!
快走  出去
Go. Get out.
走吧
Go.
对不起
他们去过那里
They were there.
发现了踪迹  但他们跑了
Caught signs, but they slipped away.
对不起
Sorry.
我以为你会很失望
I thought you'd be disappointed.
今天很成功
Well, this day was a success.
为什么
How so?
在你们走后  我继续和客人"谈了谈"
After you left, I continued the "discussion" with our guest.
他不太健谈
He wasn't too talkative.
但我问出了我想知道的一切
But I got everything I needed out of him.